windofluck.com 2016-01-05

# Wind of Luck - Free Online Naval Game With Sailing Warships - Privacy-policy

## Wind of Luck: Arena

Last Updated: 1st of August, 2013

By registering for Wind of Luck: Arena Account, using this site and/or any of Wind of Luck: Arena’s online or mobile products and services, you agree to Wind of Luck: Arena’s Privacy Policy and we may transfer and store your account information. By registering, you agree that Wind of Luck: Arena may process your data in accordance with the following privacy policy and that you will abide by Wind of Luck: Arena’s Terms of Service.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE ANY WIND OF LUCK: ARENA SITE, ONLINE OR MOBILE PRODUCT OR SERVICE. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page or other places so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material or significant changes to this policy or the way we use your child’s information, we will notify you or the parent/guardian here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Your continued use of our online and mobile products and services will signify your acceptance of the changes to our online Privacy Policy.

  * _1_

Wind of Luck: Arena Online Privacy Policy: Introduction

  * _2_

What Is Personal Information and When Does Wind of Luck: Arena Collect It?

  * _3_

What Is Non-Personal Information and When Does Wind of Luck: Arena Collect It?

  * _4_

Information Provided to Wind of Luck: Arena By Third Parties

  * _5_

What Happens To The Information Wind of Luck: Arena Collects?

  * _6_

How Does Wind of Luck: Arena Protect Your Personal Information?

  * _7_

Review, Correction of Your Information, Requesting Removal From Mailing Lists And Deactivating Your Account

  * _8_

A Special Note about Children

  * _9_

Public Information Including User Generated Content, Online Forums, Blogs And Profiles

  * _10_

Third Party Sites

  * _11_

Products Offered In Partnership With Third Party(s)

  * _12_

Contact Information

Wind of Luck: Arena and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of consumers and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted this global online Privacy Policy to explain how we store and use personal and non-personal information we collect online on our websites, during your use of our online products and/or services (including online game play) and on mobile platforms. This policy does not cover information provided online in response to job postings. 

Please note that this policy applies only to sites maintained by Wind of Luck: Arena, and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.

Wind of Luck: Arena collects both personal and non-personal consumer information. Personal information collected by Wind of Luck: Arena is discussed below in this section. Non-personal information is discussed below in Section III.

Personal information is information that identifies you and that may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. Wind of Luck: Arena may collect personal information from our online visitors during:

  * _1_

Contest registration and prize acceptance;

  * _2_

Warranty registration and requests;

  * _3_

Customer support and/or technical service requests;

  * _4_

Player match up and other head-to-head online competitions;

  * _5_

Registration for games and/or special game-specific events;

  * _6_

Newsletter subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns;

  * _7_

Registration for Wind of Luck: Arena and/or other service accounts;

  * _8_

Creation of a personal profile;

  * _9_

Product, service and/or subscription orders;

  * _10_

Service requests from third party service providers on our site; 

  * _11_

Access to our products and/or services on social networks or other third party services; and

  * _12_

Otherwise through use of our software, mobile or online services where personal information is required for use and/or participation.

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, email address, phone number, home address, birth date, mobile phone number and credit card information. In that context, your mobile number will only be used to send you a text message with a link to download your game and will not be retained for any other purpose. Prize winners may be required to provide their Social Security or other identification number for tax purposes, and will be used only for prize fulfillment.

Non-personal information, alone, cannot be used to identify or contact you. Wind of Luck: Arena collects non-personal information about your use of our online and mobile products and services both on our website and in the course of game play and software usage (on PC, mobile and game system platforms).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information contact the Privacy Policy Administrator. Please note that there may be instances where we are legally required to retain your information.

  * _A_

#### What Types of Non-Personal Information Does Wind of Luck: Arena Collect?

When you use Wind of Luck: Arena online and mobile products and services or you play our games on your PC or game system, we may collect certain non-personal demographic information including gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, game system, media, mobile device, including device IDs, incident data, Internet Protocol (IP) address, network Media Access Control (MAC) address and connection. We also collect other non-personal information such as username, user ID or persona, feature usage, game play statistics, scores and achievements, user rankings and click paths as well as other data that you may provide in surveys, via your account preferences and online profiles such as friends lists or purchases, for instance. We may also receive either non-personal or public information from third parties in connection with market and demographic studies and/or data that we use to supplement personal information provided directly by you.

  * _B_

#### How Does Wind of Luck: Arena Collect Non-Personal Information?

Wind of Luck: Arena collects non-personal information along with personal information when you actively provide it in the context of various online and mobile activities including online and mobile purchases, game registration and marketing surveys, for instance. In addition, we and other third parties use cookies and other technologies to passively collect non-personal demographic information, personalize your experience on our sites and monitor advertisements and other activities as described below. We may also derive from the information collected other facts, such as determining the applicable tax rate based on your IP address.

  * _B1_

#### Cookies

Cookies are small files applied to your Internet browser to track movements within websites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store, pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, for example. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. We and third parties collect information on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games and which ads or links are clicked. Some of our sites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are applied by our ad companies, and Wind of Luck: Arena does not have access to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so. You can set your web browser to warn you about attempts to place cookies on your computer, or limit the type of cookies you allow. 

We and other third parties may also use flash cookies, also known as “local shared objects,” on our sites that employ Flash technology. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember the site’s settings to personalize the look and feel of the site. Like normal cookies, Flash cookies are represented as small files on your computer. One method of preventing Flash cookies from being placed is to adjust your preferences in the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at [www.macromedia.com](http://www.macromedia.com/).

If you disable cookies, you may lose some of the features and functionality of playing our games, as cookies are necessary to track and enhance your game activities. Please note that companies delivering advertisements in our games or on our websites may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

Please note that this privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Wind of Luck: Arena only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * _B2_

#### Clear GIFs and Tracking Pixels

Clear GIFs (a.k.a. web bugs, beacons or tags) are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an email message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document or email message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIFs to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features or other elements on a web page. We correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages. 

We and third parties may also use tracking pixels, which allow us to advertise more efficiently by excluding our current users from certain promotional messages or identifying the source of a new installation.

  * _B3_

#### Internet Log Files

Wind of Luck: Arena and other third parties also may maintain log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that may be assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we use log files to monitor traffic on our websites and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of our websites, however we may block certain IP addresses or game system IDs provided by our licensed hardware manufacturers. If available, IP addresses and game system IDs may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Service.

  * _B4_

#### Analytic Metrics Tools and Other Technologies

Wind of Luck: Arena also uses its own proprietary analytic metrics tool and other third party analytics technologies to collect non-personal information when you use our online products and services and/or play our games on your PC, game system and/or mobile device. These tools and technologies use server log files, web beacons, cookies, tracking pixels and other tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses (including for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location), mobile or other hardware device ID, browser types, browser language, information passed from your browser (if any), referring and exit pages, and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, information about your media, software and/or applications installed on your machine and/or device, domain names and types, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the date and amount of time spent on particular pages, other Internet and website usage information, game state and the date and time of activity on our websites or games, information about how your game is used, including game metrics and statistics, feature usage and purchase history, as well as MAC Address, mobile unique device ID (if applicable) and other similar information. 

The third party analytics companies who collect information on our sites and in the context of our online and mobile products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

  * _B5_

#### Third Party Ad Serving Technology 

Wind of Luck: Arena’s websites, online or mobile products or services may employ third party ad serving technologies that use cookies, clear GIFs, web beacons, tracking pixels or other technologies to collect information as a result of ad serving through our products or services as well as to help track. Some third-party dynamic in-game advertisement serving technology enable advertising to be temporarily uploaded into your web browser or mobile device and replaced while you are online. We or third parties operating the advertisement serving technology may use demographic information such as age and gender as well as information logged from your hardware or device to ensure that appropriate advertising is presented within the site, online or mobile product or service and to calculate or control the number of unique and repeat views of a given ad, and/or deliver ads that relate to your interests and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. We or third parties may log data for this purpose including IP address (including for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location), unique device I.D., information about your software, applications and hardware, browser information (and/or information passed via your browser), hardware, machine or device make and model, advertisement(s) served, in game location, length of time an advertisement was visible, other Internet and website usage information, web pages and mobile internet sites which have been viewed by you (as well as date and time), domain type, size of the advertisement, advertisement response (if any), and angle of view. The foregoing data may be used and disclosed per this policy and the privacy policy of the company providing the ad serving technology and to other third parties in a form that does not personally identify you. 

The advertising companies who deliver ads for us may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your web browser's activities across their network of websites. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies. 

These ad serving technologies are integrated into our sites, online or mobile products and services; if you do not want to use this technology, do not play. 

Wind of Luck: Arena also obtains personal and non-personal information from third parties as discussed below. Wind of Luck: Arena only uses this data for purposes consistent with this policy.

We may receive information from third parties, including in connection with the operation and distribution of our products and services as well as market and demographic studies that we use to supplement personal and anonymous information provided directly by you. Some third party services such as Twitter and Facebook may also provide us with information from your accounts there with your permission. 

By playing a Wind of Luck: Arena game through a social network or other third party platform or service or by connecting to such a third party network, platform or service via one of our products and/or services, you are authorizing Wind of Luck: Arena to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network or other third party platform could provide to Wind of Luck: Arena through the social network/third party platform Application Programming Interface (API) based on your settings on the third party social network or platform. Your agreement takes place when you connect with the third party network, platform or service via our products and/or services, and/or when you connect with, “accept” or “allow” (or similar terms) one of our applications through a social network, or other third party platform or service.

We may also collect or receive information about you from other Wind of Luck: Arena users who choose to upload their email contacts. This information will be stored by us and used primarily to help you and your friends connect.

  * _A_

#### How Wind of Luck: Arena Uses Your Information

Wind of Luck: Arena uses your information to fulfill your specific requests, purchase orders and to send you purchase confirmation and other account-related information. In addition, the personal information you provide will allow us to send you messages about things including new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests and events of interest. You may also later opt out of certain of these communications.

Otherwise, Wind of Luck: Arena uses personal and non-personal information, both individually and combined together, to better understand the behavior and preferences of our customers, to troubleshoot technical problems, to serve static and dynamic advertising, to enforce our Terms of Service, to ensure proper functioning of our products and services as well as to help improve them. In addition, we combine non-personal information with personal information, such as an email address, to administer loyalty programs, tailor our offerings, web pages or game play experience to you. 

By use of friend finder tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Game Center or other third party services in our online products and services including mobile, you acknowledge that use of these friend finder tools will help you find your contacts and will also allow your contacts to associate your Wind of Luck: Arena Account (and related gaming entitlements, including games played on PC, mobile and console platforms) with your social networking profile and/or email address. Your resulting friends’ list, which may be accessible across Wind of Luck: Arena social platforms as available, will be subject to this privacy policy. Note that the friends that you choose to include on any Wind of Luck: Arena friends’ list may be able to find and/or identify you in the context of different Wind of Luck: Arena products and services. Choose your friends carefully.

If you choose to use our referral service to "Tell a Friend" about a Wind of Luck: Arena product or site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will send your friend an email on your behalf inviting him or her to visit the site or check out our product. Wind of Luck: Arena stores your friend's name and email for a short period for the sole purpose of sending this email and for redundancy checking, to be sure that your friend does not receive multiple copies of the same email message. We do not keep or use this information for any other purpose.

Your participation in tournaments or other online game events is also conditional upon our collection, use, storage, transmission and public display of statistical data (such as your scores, rankings and achievements) generated through your participation.

  * _B_

#### Will Wind of Luck: Arena Share My Information With Third Parties?

Wind of Luck: Arena will never share your personal information with third parties without your consent. We may, however, share anonymous, non-personal, aggregated and/or public information with third parties. There may be circumstances where you may share information on your own. Please see section IX for more details about your rights to information you share publicly on Wind of Luck: Arena and other third party sites and forums. You may also opt in to allow Wind of Luck: Arena to share your personal information with companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To opt out of further communications from a marketing partner or sponsor with whom your information has been shared, please contact that partner or sponsor directly.

Wind of Luck: Arena does not disclose any personal information about children under 18 years of age who have registered on any of our websites to third parties, or share or disclose personal information other than as set forth in this policy, provided however, that in the event of a merger, acquisition, or the unlikely event of bankruptcy, management of Wind of Luck: Arena customer information may be transferred to its successor or assign regardless of age.

From time to time, Wind of Luck: Arena employs third party contractors to collect personal information on our behalf to provide email delivery, product, prize or promotional fulfillment, contest administration, credit card processing, shipping or other services on our sites. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to our contractors. We ask some third party contractors, such as credit agencies, data analytics or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to us for our own marketing and demographic studies, so that we can consistently improve our sites and related advertising to better meet our visitors' needs and preferences. To enrich our understanding of individual customers, we tie this information to the personal information you provide to us.

When our third party agents or service providers collect and/or have access any information other than non-personal, anonymous and/or aggregated data, Wind of Luck: Arena requires that they use data consistently with our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by Wind of Luck: Arena. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your specific consent.

You will be notified before your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

We may also access and disclose personal information, including personal communications, in connection with report abuse functions in our products and services, to enforce legal rights and comply with the law, or to comply with an order from a government entity or other competent authority, or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, combat fraud and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Wind of Luck: Arena. Note that certain publically available information you post and communicate on our and third party sites and services is public information for which you have no expectation of privacy. See Section IX for more details.

The security of you and your child’s personal information is important to us. We use generally accepted methods to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and in storage. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact the Privacy Policy Administrator.

You can correct or update your account information at any time by logging on our site and navigating to “My Account,” “My Profile” or other account settings. Should you be unable to log in or wish to have your account(s) deactivated, contact the Privacy Policy Administrator. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

Some Wind of Luck: Arena sites or services may collect personal information that is not accessible via our site. However, in such cases, you may be able to access that information through alternative means of access described by the service or by writing your local privacy policy administrator at privacyadmin.ea.com and you will be contacted within 30 days regarding your request.

Wind of Luck: Arena encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without permission when using the Internet. We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. Therefore, with respect to children residing in certain jurisdictions, no information should be submitted nor posted to Wind of Luck: Arena online sites by children 12 years of age or under.

If children 12 years old and under in such jurisdictions wish to participate in online activities that require or permit the disclosure of personal information, we will request that they provide their parent or guardian's email address to notify the parent, obtain prior permission or other verifiable consent from the parent or guardian as may be necessary to participate in the activities of the site. In some other jurisdictions, notification, prior written permission or other verifiable consent may be required of a parent or guardian for children from 13 to 17 years of age.

Feedback may also be provided to Wind of Luck: Arena through “Tell us what you think” features or surveys. “Tell us what you think” collects the sender’s email address and a brief description of their concern. Email addresses obtained through “Tell us what you think” are not used for any purpose other than to respond to the sender. If we determine that the child is under 12, we will delete their email address once we have responded to their inquiry. Survey information is anonymous.

Parents may delete previously registered players at any time by emailing our support or by sending an email to the Privacy Policy Administrator.

Information collected is secured in a manner consistent with this privacy policy (see Section VI above). If we change how we handle your child’s information, we will notify you in a manner consistent with this policy.

Under no circumstances do we condition a child's participation in an activity—like contests—on the child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. On certain sites, we may not permit children to participate at all regardless of consent. Where consent is granted, consent is applicable only to that site. Regardless of jurisdiction, Wind of Luck: Arena does not disclose any personal information about children less than 18 years of age who have registered on any of our websites to third parties, or share or disclose personal information other than as set forth in this policy.

If for any reason you are concerned that your child's personally identifiable information maintained by Wind of Luck: Arena is not correct or complete, should you wish to have your child's personal information deleted from our records, or if you want Wind of Luck: Arena to discontinue further collection or use of your child's personal information, please contact the Privacy Policy Administrator. The Privacy Policy Administrator will be happy to review, update or remove your child's information as appropriate.

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to Wind of Luck: Arena sites or games or in our online chat rooms, blogs, message boards, user “profiles” for public view or in similar forums on our sites and/or on third party sites. Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. 

You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit in the course of these public activities can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to make public in any of these forums.

Note also that in the ordinary course of Internet activity, certain information may be sent from your browser to third parties such as advertising networks and analytics companies. Wind of Luck: Arena has no control over the information sent from your browser to those networks or other third parties and recommends that you ensure that your browser settings prevent the disclosure of information you would not like to share.

If you post a video, image or photo on one of our sites for public view you should be aware that these may be viewed, collected, copied and/or used by other users without your consent. We are not responsible for the videos, images or photos that you choose to submit to Wind of Luck: Arena’s site. Please see our Terms of Service on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our websites.

Our website may contain advertising or services which link to other websites such as Twitter, Facebook and YouTube. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the Wind of Luck: Arena site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as Wind of Luck: Arena. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to a Wind of Luck: Arena site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.

Members may register for other services from our site(s). Certain products and/or services available on our site are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact Trazzy Entertainment Privacy Policy Administrator ([privacy@trazzy.com](mailto:%20privacy@trazzy.com)) or write to:

#### Privacy Policy Administrator

Trazzy Entertainment Ltd.  
Georgiou Gennadiou, 10  
AGATHANGELOS COURT  
Office 403  
3041, Limassol, Cyprus IR  

For more information and updates to our online Privacy Policy, visit [www.windofluck/privacy-policy.php](http://www.windofluck/privacy-policy.php).
